继   承   之   战
第 3 季  第 8 集
仅向执行董事和董事会成员
开放的下车点
感谢配合
洛根想耽误你们几分钟  可以吗
Oh, could Logan just get five?
欢迎  你爸还好吗
Welcome. How's your dad?
挺好的
Oh, pretty good.
他希望下次能亲自拜访
He hopes to make it in person to the next one.
当然  代我向他问好    -我会的
-Oh, sure. Send him my best. -I will.
不过  你来了就很好
But still, you're here, and that's nice.
谢谢  我也这么觉得
Thanks. I feel the same way.
好极了  大家都乐翻天了吧    -怎么回事
Great. We're all over the fucking moon. -What is this?
当然了  我们正在讨论收购 Gojo
-Yeah.  So we are in discussions to acquire GoJo.
好吧
Okay.
进展如何    -没那么快
How advanced?  Oh, not that advanced.
只是在谈框架条款
Just getting to outline terms.
也就是很有进展的意思了
So pretty fucking advanced?
没有实质进展 我们也不想打扰二位
Well, we didn't wanna bother you until we have some protein.
但我们也不想在董事会上 打你们个措手不及
But we didn't wanna ambush you in the boardroom.
我们想 先在这告知你们
We wanted to let you know in here.
可你们这还是在搞突袭啊
But you are still ambushing us.
不不不  我们没有
-No... We are not ambushing.
我是说
-Well, no, I mean...
如果你半夜突然跳到街上
if you jump out on someone on the road in the middle of the night
打破了别人的脑袋 还大喊
hit them on the head and shout
"我没搞突袭"  那也算是突袭
"I'm not ambushing you." It's still a fucking ambush.
我爱我的事业
I love my business.
但二十年里 我们都被广告业压榨死尽
But we've had our throats slit on ads for 20 years.
我们遍体鳞伤了
We're bleeding out.
有线电视服务再停五年
Another five of cord-cutting
我们就他妈死无葬身之地了
and we'll be dead on the fucking carpet.
这是场革命性的交易
This is a transformative deal.
可是 但 这显然...不合理
Yeah, but, just obviously, this is not okay.
我们本应该参与交易决策
We were supposed to be inside deal-making.
我们进展太快了
Well, you know, we're moving very fast
事情很敏感
and it's all very sensitive,
但我保证...-他们差不多到齐了
but I assure... -I think they're assembling.
行 那我们走吧
-Right. Shall we?
好的 那 如果...马特森又开始药劲上头
Okay. How will you feel if Matsson starts micro-dosing
发 有关天使[投资]的 推文怎么办
and tweeting about angels again?
马特森是有眼力的人
Matsson's a visionary.
可不  他都飘飘欲仙了
Sure. Because he's trippin' balls.
不 他的团队值得我们来合作
Well, he has a team we can do business with.
这事情的重要程度超乎想象
This is bigger than anything you've ever contemplated.
这会重塑整个公司
It will reshape the company entirely.
如果你们 真的 真的 不满意...
Well, if you guys really, really don't like it...
好吧  那就算了
sure. Kill it.
我们可没这么说
Well, we didn't say that.
那  我们  总算能走了吗
So? Shall we? Finally?
小西对此是什么看法  为什么小西不在
Wait, where is Shiv on this? Why isn't Shiv here?
因为这事仅限集团核心讨论
Oh, because this is just inner circle.
开玩笑呢  我在开玩笑
That's a joke, I'm kidding.
总裁会来参加的  所以...
I think the President will be joining us, so...
什么事    -你好啊
-Yeah? -Hey. So...
我觉得他们会接受
I think they're gonna eat it.
桑蒂在消化信息  斯图伊很喜欢
Sandi is processing, Stewy loves it,
罗曼主导  卡尔 弗兰克都不在
Roman led. No Karl, no Frank.
桑蒂想听你的看法
Sandi wants your take,
格丽想要接过你的职责
Gerri's trying to fill your boots
可桑蒂似乎不买账
but I don't think Sandi's buying it
我正跟着他们去开董事会
and I'm just following them now to the boardroom.
你在车里吗
You in the car?
不  我线上参会
No. I'm gonna call in.
也可以  没什么事吧  亲爱的
Well, that works. Is everything okay, honey?
没事  我只是
Yeah, I just...
我还是之前那感觉  所以..
I'm feeling the way I was feeling still, so...
你妈的婚礼 怎样了
What about your mom's wedding?
我感觉不太好
I'm not feeling great,
所以 没什么好说的
so there's nothing really to say.
好吧 好吧
Right.
可能你根本不需要去呢
Well, maybe you don't even really need to go.
不去妈的婚礼吗
To Mom's wedding?
对啊
Oh, yeah.
绝对不行 她会叨叨一辈子的
fuck that, I'd never hear the end of it.
你能想象吗
Can you imagine?
那么 没法到会的董事会成员
So, the board members not physically available
将通过电话参会
will be joining by phone
包括西沃恩·罗伊  她向各位表达歉意
including Siobhan Roy, who sends her apologies
她在研究策略
she's working on strategy.
以及肯德尔·罗伊.   -大家好
And Kendall Roy...  -Hey.
好的  肯德尔·罗伊因病无法参会
-Hey.  And Kendall Roy who's not attending due to illness.
那我们就开始...   一派胡言
-And we're gonna lead off... -That's not actually true.
那我们就首先讨论
And we're gonna lead off with an update
正在顺利进行的调查的最新进展
on the promising developments in the ongoing investigation
这部分会议的内容
from which portion of the meeting
肯德尔和洛根·罗伊是被要求回避的
Kendall and Logan Roy are recused. Hence...
然后我们将会讨论收购事宜
and then we'll move on to discuss acquisitions.
他就这么看着吗
Is he gonna watch?
我觉得自己像是在古根海姆博物馆拉屎  朋友们
I feel like I'm taking a shit in the Guggenheim, y'all.
我们能在会议记录里写 他在监视我们吗
Could we make a note in the minutes that he's watching us?
你好啊  我认识你
Hey, I know you.
我记得你以前好像是西沃恩·罗伊吧
Didn't you used to be Siobhan Roy?
你在董事会上  听着像个傻子
You sounded dumb at the board meeting.
至少我出现了 你干吗去了
At least I showed up. What were you doing?
和别的傀儡女总裁吃了早午餐吗
Brunching with some other sock puppet girl-boss presidents?
你没人约吗  拉亚 [邀请制社交平台] 上面
You haven't got a date?
没人愿意来意大利 骑在你软趴趴的鸡巴上吗
Did no one on Raya wanna come to Italy and sit on your Ricotta dick?
这么说吧  我暗中调查了一下彼得·洋葱
So? Just to say, I had... Peter Onions rat-fucked.
多好的结婚礼物啊
Oh, what a lovely wedding present.
那家伙就是块狗皮膏药
The guy's a fucking slime badger.
三次破产  两次婚姻  四个孩子
Three bankruptcies, two marriages, four children
还有五家空壳公司
and five shell companies.
他是一家垃圾疗养院的大股东
He's a big investor in shitty nursing homes
把苹果酱倒进老人的食道
tipping applesauce down their gullets
还骗他们说  吃的是四道菜的大餐
and telling them they had a four-course dinner.
总是这样   -没错
-All the hits. -Yup.
所以我问了妈妈  能不能和她谈谈
So, I've asked Mom if we can talk to her
我们应该一起去
and I think we should do it together.
去干吗
Do what?
还“去干吗“啊 就
"Do what?" like...
问她到底该不该结这个婚
ask her if she should be doing this, you know.
从罗里本该搬过来才过了五个月
It's like, five months since Rory was supposed to move in.
管他呢
Whatever.
或者我们至少
Or we can at least
看她有没有签婚前协议
check that she's getting a prenup.
离婚要涉及到的破事可多了
You know, there's a lot of shit in there from the divorce
控股公司之类的
the holding company and everything.
这家伙显然是有所图谋  所以  要出手吗
And the guy is clearly on the make, so, yeah?
管他的
fuck it.
真..管他的
So... fuck it?
对
Yeah.
她可能成了他的性奴
She's probably in sexual thrall to him
他的大屌让她疯狂
he's driving her wild with his sugar dick
好极了   -所以我们无能为力
and so there's nothing that we can do.
好吧
All right, fine.
那就任他 为了绿宝石杀掉她
Let him kill her for her emeralds
然后把我们赶出公司  我不介意
and screw us out of the fucking firm see if I care.
小罗  关于那笔交易
Hey, Rome? About the deal?
我跟卡尔和弗兰克谈过
I was talking to Karl and Frank.
行  但你其实不算内部的一员  你俩都不算
Yeah, no, but you're not really a part of that, either of you.
我算
Well, I am.
我现在还不能解雇你  小西
Well, I can't quite fire you yet, Shiv
因为我还有点害怕你
because I'm still a little bit scared of you.
可我的想法是  等我接手
But my thinking is when I take over
我要把你放在我隔壁的办公室
I'm gonna put you in the office next to mine
让你做我的性感秘书
and you're gonna be my sexy secretary.
你他妈什么毛病
The fuck is wrong with you?
我不知道  我们也在研究
I dunno. We're working on it.
正在进行时
Ongoing process.
欢迎  跟着我
-Welcome. Follow me. -Let's go.
稍等一下
Just a minute.
你好  你好  妈
-Hello. -Hey, Mom.
你好  欢迎你们
Hello, welcome all.
我的天啊
Goodness me.
你是刚从前线回来吗
Did you just come back from the front?
对  是这种感觉
Yeah. Just felt like it.
正准备抛下一切
It's dripping down.
挺好的
It's nice.
你好  宝贝们  你们好吗
Hello, darlings. How are you?
见到你们真高兴
How lovely to see you.
你看起来真帅气
Don't you look lovely?
你们都会被带进房子
So, you're all going to be taken up to the house.
我很快过去  孩子们
-I'll be there in a minute, guys.
你看起来很累
You look rather tired.
谢谢  要聊聊吗
Thanks. You wanted a word?
对  是的
Right. Yes.
听着  我想问你的是
So listen, what I wanted to ask you
你去房子那 就能看到
you'll see when you go up to the house
彼得打印出来的
that Peter has printed out
满满当当的 可怕日程安排
this awful sort of itinerary of events.
欢迎仪式  然后排练
Welcoming and the rehearsals,
还有正式典礼  还有
and the ceremonies, and...
还有
And
我在想 能不能稍微分摊一下
I wondered if we couldn't slightly divvy them up?
分摊什么  -分摊
-As in?   -As in...
据我所知  你父亲不想
your father would rather not as I understand it,
和你待一起  离得越远越好
be together with you as far as possible.
所以...
And so,
你儿子会得到什么
what is your son getting
你痛恨的前夫  又会得到什么
and what is your ex-husband, who you hate, getting?
请不要这么盛气凌人
Please don't get on your high horse.
不是我的意思  我不在乎  是那位..
It's not me, I don't mind. It's
难缠的新郎
"Bridezilla."
他一心想着
He's got his heart set
请所有重要人物参加他的婚礼
on having all the important people at his wedding.
真是个小骚包
-He's such a little tart.
我不知道这样是否行得通
-Well, I don't know if that works.
拜托  考虑一下
Please, have a think.
我们还有很多见面的机会
And I'll still see you tons.
对吗
Yeah?
彼得
Peter!
过来和肯德尔打个招呼
Come and say hello to Kendall.
肯德尔像块薄荷糕
Kendall, like the mint cake.
很高兴见到你   -彼此彼此
-Yeah. Pleased to meet you. -Absolutely.
好了  妈  我看看行程表
Okay. Mom, I'll check the schedule,
也许下个月再见吧
maybe see you next month.
拜托  别这么夸张  很高兴见到你
-Come on, don't be so dramatic. -Nice to meet you.
就四个小时而已  肯德尔
It's gonna be about four hours, Kendall.
你好
-Hello. -Hello.
你好  我是格丽·吉尔曼
Hello, I'm Gerri Kellman. How...
我是维奥拉  很高兴见到你   -很高兴见到你
-I am Viola. -Nice to meet you. -Nice to meet you.
这里真不错
-This is very nice.
好地方
What a place.
意大利披萨 意大利面 和教皇
Italy! Pizza, pasta, and Popes.
你见过教皇吗  老康
You ever met the Pope, Con?
见过
Yeah.
见过一位
I met one,
几任之前的教皇  和我爸一起
couple of popes back, with Dad.
他是个纯正的教皇
He was a real full-fat Pope.
十足的教皇
Complete Pope.
十分虔诚
Very religious.
他被彻底洗脑了  对吧
I guess he really drank the Kool Aid, huh?
真漂亮
Wow. It's pretty.
一切都好吧  老康
Everything okay, Con?
还好  挺好
Yup. Yeah.
只是
Just
政客网那人在问  有关他报道的事
the guy from Politico... asking regarding his piece,
你的全名 工作经历
your full name and, like, your employment history
之类的东西   -好吧
-and whatnot. -Oh, right.
你觉得他是想挖猛料吗  -也许只是出于好意
-You think he's digging? -Might be friendly.
但是 你知道的
But, you know,
也许不是  你觉得呢
probably not. What do you think?
对  也许是好意吧
Yeah, it's probably friendly.
因为根据我的经验
Because journalists are so fucking friendly
记者都太他妈友善了
in my experience.
好了
Okay.
你好
Hey.
要去欢迎酒会吗
Going to the welcome drinks?
当然  我先跟劳里待一会儿
Sure. Let me just check on Laurie
然后我和你可以集思广益一下 Gojo 的价码
and then you and I can put our heads together on the GoJo price.
好的   -时间紧迫  但没什么好怕的
It's ticking up, but nothing scary.
劳里 劳里 劳里
Laurie...
你总是没完没了地念叨他
You just will not stop going on about him.
我觉得你走火入魔了  坦白说  这很恶心
I think you're obsessed, and frankly, it's disgusting.
劳里  我们要下去了
Laurie? We're gonna walk down.
你能跟上吗   -好的 可以
-Can you catch up? -Yeah.
好的  很好
-Okay. -Okay. Cool.
好了 所以 听着
Okay. So look,
我得跟你谈谈   -好
I need to talk to you. Hi.
我...我有事情要问你   -好的
-I need to ask you something. -Okay.
你别再给我发那些..东西了
I need you to stop sending me the items.
哪些东西
The which?
我的屌照吗
The dick pics?
你...不想看我鸡巴的照片吗
-Don't want pictures of my dick?
不想   -好吧
-No.  Okay.
有被冒犯到  你确定吗
-Kind of offended. Are you sure?
是的 我确定   -好的
-Yes, I'm sure.  -Okay.
我他妈是认真的  罗曼
-I'm fucking serious, Roman.
我不太确定  我觉得你其实想看
I'm not so sure, I feel like you do want them
你这是典型的欲擒故纵
but you're being kind of typically minxy.
我姑且认为  你压力大时会这样...
I think this happens when you're under pressure or...
但 你得找找别的宣泄出口  罗曼
but you need to find some other outlet, Roman.
看看你  想要揣测我的想法
Look at you, trying to get inside my head.
不要打开潘多拉的盒子
Don't open Pandora's Box.
里面只有更多的鸡巴
There's just more dicks in there.
不  她的房子很漂亮  非常
Okay, she has a lovely house, quite.
你好  妈妈   抱歉
Hey, mother. -Sorry.
罗曼   -你好
-Roman! -Hi.
你好
-Hello.
罗曼 你认识彼得的
-Roman, you know Peter.
是的   -是的
Yup.
彼得  罗曼担心我要失去自我了
Peter, Roman's worried in case I'm throwing myself away.
他觉得 我为你神魂颠倒
He thinks I'm in thrall to you.
恰恰相反
Other way around.
你怎么样
Well, how you doing?
对于这一切 非常兴奋
Very excited about all this.
是的 是的 当然 我也是
Yeah, yeah, of course. Me too.
还有 生意怎么样
And how's business?
听说你的银发“古拉格劳改营“办得风生水起啊
I hear you're big in the old Silvery Gulags?
是的 在帮助一个养老院集团扭亏为盈
Yes. Helping to turn around a nursing home group.
我们..这很有意义
We... It's very rewarding.
参与其中...
Come in...
监督它的运作 裁减冗员
look at the operations, trim the fat.
是的  -他指的是护士
-Yeah. -He means the nurses.
她很失礼  也不知道我怎么能忍受的
She's very rude. I don't know why I put up with it.
我对你也很失礼
And I'm very rude to you too.
他很糟糕  我看得出来
He is awful, I can obviously see that.
不不不   一点也不  他正是你喜欢的类型
No. No... not at all. He's actually just your type.
继爸之后  又一个上流社会的英国伪君子
Another in the line of post-dad posh, English phonies.
他不属于上流社会  他父亲是名医生
He's not posh. His father's a doctor.
自力更生[自己买家具]
Bought all his own furniture.
靠奖学金为生的贪婪男孩
Yeah, he's a grasping little scholarship boy.
好了  口下留情  妈妈
Well, take it easy there, Mother.
你说的可是我的继父
That's my stepfather you're talking about.
都是他逼我的  举办什么托斯卡纳婚礼
He's forcing me into all of this, this Toscana bit.
但他确实十分有趣!!  他
But he is tremendous fun. I mean, look at him
像瓶廉价的普罗塞克葡萄酒一样  斯斯冒泡
fizzing away over there like a bottle of cheap prosecco.
非常廉价
Very cheap.
妈妈
Mom?
你知道 我不善言辞
Well, you know that I'm not a big one for saying things
但我想说你
but I'm just gonna say, are you...
你确定吗  这家伙有四个孩子
Are you sure? The guy has, like, four kids.
可不止那些  亲爱的
He's got a lot more than that, my darling.
很好 太棒了
Oh, great. That's fantastic.
你们有婚前协议的 对吧
There's a prenup though, right?
拜托 别这么没情调
Oh, come on. Don't be so unromantic.
妈妈  只是... 我担心你操之过急了
Mom, just... I'm concerned that maybe you're rushing this.
那你想让我靠什么活下去
So what do you expect me survive on?
通心粉和追悼会吗
Macaroni and memorial services?
失陪一下
Excuse me for a second.
所以呢
So?
是啊 她说她不能
Yeah, she says she can't
靠通心粉和追悼会活下去
live off macaroni and memorial services.
可怜的埃莉诺·里戈比 想要翻云覆雨
Wow, poor old Eleanor Rigby wants to eat dick and drink champagne
喝香槟度过余生吗
for the rest of her life instead?
显然 我们讨厌彼得
Yeah. Apparently we're meant to hate Peter
是因为他够聪明  能拿到奖学金
because he was smart enough to get a scholarship
还能自力更生
and bought his own furniture.
还有什么  有...有什么要求吗
What else do we got? Any requests?
有邀约吗   -没有 并没有
-Any offers? -No, not really.
有一个座谈会
There's a sit-down,
类似播客..
like a podcast
基本上就像...   -好的
that's basically like
类似前环球报记者做的..
ex-Globe journalists who are doing sort of like a...
类似肯尼迪家族的报道
kind of like the Kennedys.
罗伊的诅咒 "深度报道"
Curse of the Roys, deep dive.
他们在调查康纳的妈妈 还有
They're doing Connor's mom, and...
你爸和一个叫露丝的人
your dad and someone named Rose
还有小报自杀事件
and then the tabloid suicides.
那个被霸凌的孩子
There's like a kid who was bullied
是意外死亡 还是自杀
and was it an accident or did he kill himself?
他好像是你妹妹婚礼上的侍应生
He was the caterer at your sister's wedding, I guess.
你知道这件事吗
You know about this?
当然
Sure.
好的 所以他们在向整个家族的人发送请求
Right, so they're spraying requests around the whole family.
也许
Maybe
盯紧这个内容 好吗   -好的
keep tabs on that one. -Okay? -Okay.
这些卑鄙小人们
fucking bottom feeders.
那 没事的话 我可以先滚吗
So, unless it's weird, I might fuck off?
好 随便你
Yeah. Whatever.
下班滚蛋吧   -好的
Clock the fuck off. Okay.
好啊
Okay.
不错 我们还好吗
-Very nice. How we doing? -Yeah.
很好 很棒啊
-Good, great. Yeah. -Absolutely.
我很好
-Yeah. -I'm great.
糟了
Oh, shit.
手机总不让人消停   -对 抱歉
-Phone stuff. Yeah... -Yeah. Sorry.
没事 没事 去吧
No, no, go for it.
谢谢你  -恭喜你啊 格雷格
Well, congratulations, Greg.
是啊 和你不是一个量级的 癞蛤蟆想吃天鹅肉
Yeah. Punching above your weight?
你说小康吗
Oh, Comfry?
对 对啊
Oh, yeah...
对 我喜欢她
Yeah, I like her.
但 我在想..
I do wonder...
能帮我拿着吗  这段感情有交心吗
Can you hold this?  -...is there depth there?
当然   -就是...我不知道...是有意义的吗
-Sure.  Like is... I don't... Like, is there substance?
交心
Depth?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
一个近乎渴死的男人
The man dying of thirst
瞬间变成了矿泉水评论家
is suddenly a mineral water critic?
小康没有满足你对智慧的渴望吗  格雷格
Does Comfry not sate your lust for wisdom, Greg?
真遗憾 桑塔格[作家] 不在世了
Such a shame Sontag's not still alive.
不然你就能带她体验下 得来速麦当劳汽车餐厅了
You could take her to the drive-though.
或是 我在想
Maybe I wonder
一旦她认识到“真实的我"
when she gets to know the "real me"
她还会留在我身边吗
will she stick around?
我觉得 不管怎样 就算成不了
Well, I guess either way if doesn't work out,
她是个很棒的约会敲门砖
she's a great date ladder.
什.. 什么意.. 意思
Excuse me? As in...
就是当别人看到你们在一起
Well, you know, people will see her with you.
无意冒犯啊  他们会说
And no offense, but they'll say,
这他妈的什么情况
"What the fuck's going on there?"
他凭什么站在她身边
-"Why is he with her?"
是的 我明白 你们的意思
-Yes. Yeah. Yeah, I'm aware of what you're saying.
好的   -对 你还是有好处的
-Yeah. Okay. -It still could work for you.
约会敲门砖  这游戏不错
Date ladder. Play the date ladder game.
那...她怎么样
What about her?
她看起来不错   -确实
She looks nice. -Yeah.
是啊  有何不可呢
-Yeah.  -I mean, yeah, why not?
她很漂亮   -她确实非常漂亮
-She's pretty.  -She is very pretty.
她还是个公主或女伯爵什么的
-She is also a princess or a duchess or something,
是吗   -可以啊 是啊
but sure. Yeah.
为什么不呢  有何不可呢
-Why not? -What?  Why not?
我们都把人送上月球了
We put a man on the moon.
-好吧  -好吧
-Okay. -Okay. Wow.
可怜的女人  她可能
Poor woman, she probably...
她以为自己在婚礼上遇到了有趣的家伙
She thinks she met a fun guy at a wedding.
他应该像只危险的蜥蜴一样遍体通红
He should be colored red like a dangerous lizard.
别 啊 恐怖保姆开始军事演习了
Oh, no, Scary Poppins is on maneuvers.
你能... 就是
Can you, you know,
挡住我吗   -挡住你吗
just block me from her?  -Blocking you.
她知道我目前处境不好
You know, she knows that I'm not in a good place
就会过来给我整一出...
and then it's all
十面埋伏  你懂吗
house of flying daggers, you know.
当然   -"你的婚姻幸福吗"
-Sure. -"How's your marriage going?
你有打算要孩子吗
-Are you gonna have children?"
所以 你的婚姻幸福吗
-How is your marriage going?
你有打算要孩子吗
Are you gonna have children?
好  很好笑
Okay. Ha-ha.
是 卡洛丽娜
Karolina.
前往澳门  感觉手气不错
Going to Macau, feeling lucky.
汤姆  是马特森
Tom. Matsson.
什么  前往澳门   -他妈的
-What? Going to Macau? -The fuck.
感觉手气不错  这他妈的搞什么
Feeling lucky? What the fuck is that?
你看到卡洛丽娜发来的吗
-You see this thing from Karolina? -Did you see this?
先是玩失踪  现在又这
It's off the radar and now this?
这..这是他的行动吗
Is this a move?
这可能
It... it could be...
这可能是虚惊一场  好吗
it could be nothing, you know.
傻逼社交媒体 烟雾弹而已
fucking social media fireworks.
前往澳门 感觉手气不错
Going to Macau, feeling lucky.
他是想抬价吗
-Is he trying to boost his price? -Yeah.
他是在捣乱  还是想搞黄交易啊
Is he just rocking the boat or trying to blow up the deal?
难道他网站的用户数量水涨船高了吗
I mean, has he got a good subscriber numbers coming in?
或许他真的是要去澳门
Maybe he's just going to Macau
而且感觉手气不错吧
and he's feeling lucky.
或是
Maybe...
喂  卢卡斯  打给我  你嗑大了吗
Hey, Lukas, call me. Are you high?
我觉得 你该少喝点超大杯的死滕水[致幻剂]了
I think you should put down the venti ayahuasca Big Gulp.
我们得知道推文是怎么回事 好吗 兄弟
We need to be inside track on these tweets, man, okay?
打给我
Call me.
我不知道 他这人就是这样
I don't know, it's like it's his thing.
他...他就是个捣蛋鬼魔术师
-He's a trickster.
好吧 很好  那他会
-Okay. Well, sounds cool. Is he gonna, like,
偷走我们的手表 然后把交易一切两半吗
steal our watches and saw the fucking deal in half?
有可能
Maybe.
你应该了解内情啊  小罗
You're supposed to be inside this, Rome.
我的确  是啊  你别管了
I am inside this. Leave it.
干得不错  小罗
Hey, nice work, Rome.
你好
Hey.
马特森疯了
Matsson going nut-nut.
紧紧看好他兄弟
Keep hold of that shit, bro.
都在我掌控之下  混蛋
It's all under control, motherfucker.
是吗 是的你要去哪儿
-Yeah? -Yeah.  Where are you off to?
去那不勒斯买点能嗑的吗
Naples, score some junk?
不是  咱妈把我赶出了  她的宴会
No, just our mother throwing me out of her party.
不错
-Oh, nice. Good.
很好  那再见   -我的孩子在哪
Well, so long. -Where are my kids?
你们知道我的孩子们在哪吗
Hey, hey, guys, where the fuck are my kids?
真令人惊讶   肯不知道他的孩子在哪
What a surprise? Ken doesn't know where his kids are.
听着  我一直在想
So look, I've been thinking...
谁知道之后会发生什么
who knows what'll happen...
或许我不会大获成功
maybe I won't ignite?
或许两党制没有看起来那么腐败
Maybe the two party system isn't as rotten as it looks.
但我必须为成功做好计划  所以 威拉
But I have to plan for success. So, Willa...
这让我很难启齿
this is a difficult conversation to have.
好吧
Oh, okay.
所以  你没问题吗
So you're okay?
对  我不...  你说吧...
Yeah, I don't... Just, no, go on and just...
我们可以重新做回地下恋
We can go back underground, you know?
我在市区的公寓而你来找我这
Me in my apartment in the city, you come visit.
挺浪漫的
-It's kind of romantic?
这样行不通  不行
-That doesn't work for me. No.
好吧   -马克西姆有个想法
-Okay. -Maxim had an idea...
那就是
which is...
你愿意让我成为
will you make me
世上最快乐的男人
the most happiest man...
以及最刀枪不入的候选人吗
slash most bulletproof candidate in the world?
好的
Oh, okay.
好的   -不是  我..意思是
-Okay? -Oh, no, I... No, I mean...
宝贝
Baby.
人们都在看  威拉
People are looking, Willa.
那么  我很乐意地说...
Well, then I'd be pleased to say...
好的  我愿意  可以给我.
yes... yes. Can I...
可以给我点时间 考虑下吗
Can I have a little think on it?
那既然这样
If it's okay,
我就当你答应了一样..   -好的
I'm smiling now.  Right.
维持笑容
Like you said yes.
好
Okay.
你慢慢想   -好的
-But take your time. -Right.
Gojo 的价格在不断攀升
So GoJo's price is moving up and fucking up.
好  我觉得他骗了你  小罗
Yeah. I think he played you, Rome.
这会被证交会打得死死的
SEC's gonna be all over this.
是啊  我的老天爷啊
Oh, yeah, oh, my goodness
不过是 被该死的婴儿啃了 不痛不痒
gummy love bite from the fucking toddlers.
我觉得他喜欢我们  我打从心底这么认为
I think he likes us, I do, I can feel that in my gut.
好  又一条
Okay. Another one.
表情符号  遥控器  手指交叉[求好运]  茄子
Emojis, controller, fingers crossed, eggplant.
或许  他是想..操一个游戏网站
Maybe he's trying to fuck a gaming site something with...
听着  小罗  情况很糟
Rome, this is bad.
我...我觉得没问题
-I... I think we're good.
是吗  如果他搞砸了交易  我们还能找谁
-Oh, yeah? If he blows this deal, then who is left for us exactly?
我们可能会沧落为
We could become the fucking
泛美韦斯达   -百视达 一个靠拨号卖片的企业
Pan-American  Waystar-Blockbuster Video dial-up Corporation.
好的
Okay.
他来了
Here he comes.
她也来了
And here she comes.
他一点也
He does not give a single
对 不他妈的在乎
-No.  ...solitary fuck.
对   -或许什么也没发生
-No. -Maybe it's all fine.
或许他们只是躺一张床
Maybe they just share a big bed together
看看老友记的重播  喝着奶昔
and they watch Friends reruns and drink milkshakes.
看来你父亲顺利抵达了
-Oh, hi. -Well, your father made it -it would appear.
所以 你知道报道的事吗
-And you know the story?
什么报道  就这讨厌鬼猪头和姘头
What? The skunk, the porcupine, and the concubine?
真是我收到最好的结婚礼物了
Probably the best wedding present I'll ever get.
但...真恶心
But so disgusting.
他还在操玛西娅吗  你们认为呢
Is he still fucking Marcia, do we think?
我不这么认为   -希望如此
-I think not is the word. -Hope not,
可怜的老东西  可能会因为太过激动昏死过去
poor old fellow  would probably keel over with the effort.
好了  我要去告诉大家
Oh, well, I gotta go around telling everybody
说话要小心谨慎
to be very discreet.
对了  小西
Oh, and Shiv
你知道接下来会发生什么糟心事吗
you know about this awful thing later on?
我和小罗有..
Oh, yeah... Rome and I have...
我们有正事要做所以..
Have got a big...we're working on a big deal
我们刚被鱼雷袭击了[破坏了交易]
and so we just got hit by a torpedo
-所以 这事我不能...   -小西 别傻了
-and it's not okay, I think. -Oh, Shiv, don't be silly.
跟老妈去玩吧  我能搞定
Go have fun with Mom, I can manage. It's...
这...她其实根本没那么重要
She's not even that involved.
是吗
Yeah?
那待会见   -不客气
See you later.  You're welcome.
去你的   -洛根 你来啦
fuck you.  -Logan, you came.
你还好吗
-How you doing?
还在和国税局斗智斗勇
Staying ahead of the Inland Revenue?
欢迎光临托斯卡纳
-Welcome to Toscana.
很高兴来此地
-Oh, glad to be here.
有任何需要我的地方 尽管开口
Anything I can do, just let me know.
有心了
Very kind.
方便的时候我想跟你私下谈谈
When we get the chance I wanted a discreet word with you
你在英国政府那边的联系人
about your contacts in UK government.
我只是
It's just
想回报 为您提供服务
I'd like to give something back, you know the chance to serve.
洛根
Logan.
他有什么企图
And what did he want?
他想让我跟唐宁街那群笨蛋取得联系
He wants me to get the dipshits on Downing Street
封他为 他妈的 诡异性癖王
to make him Lord fucking Seat Sniffer Pantyhose.
你看推文了吗   -看了
-Did you read the tweet? -Yup.
你们谈过了吗   -试过了  但..
-Have you spoken? -Tried, but...
我不习惯通过茄子来谈判
I'm not used to negotiating via eggplant.
我不确定他是否想要这笔交易
I'm not sure he wants the deal.
他可能只是在恶搞我们
He might just run a fucking moussaka.
你要我再给他打个电话吗
You want to try calling him again?
好吧
Okay.
只要他不来这里
As long as he doesn't come here.
不行  你还好吗
-No. Hey, hey, you okay?
我很好  爸
-Yeah. I'm okay. Hey, Dad.
肯  他不想见你
Ken, he doesn't wanna see you.
他不想跟你说话
He doesn't wanna talk to you.
你简直在放屁
-Yeah, this is all total horseshit.
我们说好的  老天爷啊
-We had a deal. Jesus Christ.
我们把话说开了 行吗
Let's just have it out, okay?
我要见你爸  我们晚饭时见
I wanna see you, Dad, I wanna see you for dinner
把这事敲定好吗
and let's just nail this, okay?
晚上八点
8.00,
一个人来好吗
on your own. Yeah?
他很忙
He's busy.
可不   -我们稍后再回复他
-Sure. -We'll get back to him.
我们稍后再回复你
We'll get back to you.
你们稍后回复我
Oh. You'll get back to me?
混蛋
You prick.
我该去吗
Should I go?
说不上来  也许穿上防刺背心
I don't know, maybe wear a stab vest.
我的意思是 你应该去
I mean, it'll be okay. Maybe you should go.
把他踢出公司
Get him out of the firm.
要我跟你一起去吗   一边儿去吧
-You want me to come with you? -Oh, fuck off.
我才不怕  给我找几间空房
I'm not scared. Get me some rooms
我要给马特森打个电话
-I wanna get Matsson on the phone. -Okay.
你好  欢迎欢迎
Hello, welcome.
就快到了
We're almost there.
好啊
-Hey,
抱歉..   -好啊
I'm sorry. -Oh, hi.
有点忙
Hey, just busy.
终于忍痛脱身了
Managed to tear yourself away?
你觉得彼得的女儿怎么样
What do you think of Peter's daughters?
他们都是室内设计师
They're both in interior design.
失业在家
They're unemployed.
是啊  她们主动提出...帮我拍照
Yeah. They offered to take photos
顺便偷了我手机里的联络人
and I think they exported my address book.
不会吧   -就是
-No. -Yeah.
老天爷
God.
这场单身派对
The bachelorette party.
我妈的馆材板要按不住了
My mother would turn in her grave.
小罗有点在意
Hey, Rome is kind of concerned.
你的婚前财产协议应该很牢靠  对吧
You do have a watertight prenup, right?
你觉得他会为了外婆的鲁本斯假画害我吗
Do you think he's gonna do me in for Granny's fake Rubens?
至少你的律师不是吃素的吧
-You've got a good lawyer at least.
当然  事实上  我正打算启封跟你爸的离婚协议
-Yeah. Sure. I'm actually having to open up the divorce agreement
因为彼得看上了伊顿广场的公寓
with your father. because Peter loves Eaton Square flat.
他自己没有房子吗
Does he not got one his own?
他运气不好
He had a bit of bad luck
做烟熏三文鱼亏了本
with a salmon-smoking business
卖掉了皮姆利科伦敦的房子
and he lost his place in Pimlico.
真有生意头脑啊
Quite the business brain.
他心胸宽广
Got a very big heart.
真是异性相吸啊
Well, I supposed opposites attract.
我们能好好抽根烟吗
Should we just enjoy a fag?
暂时不要互相放冷枪了
And not do any sniping for a bit?
还是说你只是想得到我的注意
Or have you come to get some attention?
我需要你的注意  省省吧
Me? Attention from you? Oh, no.
那都是几百年前的事
That ship sailed long ago.
我可能不是一个好母亲
Yeah. I might have been a bit of a spotty mother
但你也不是什么省油的灯  所以.
but you've been a shitty daughter, so...
你也没那么糟  你只是..
You weren't a spotty mother,  you were just an
总是不在场  但我很好
absence... but I'm fine.
为了能和你近一点 我搬回了纽约
I moved back to bloody New York so I could be near you
但我却从没见过你
-and I never fucking saw you.
妈  没事的
-Mom, it's okay.
我很好
It's fine,
你让爸抚养我们  或许是最好的选择
you let Dad take us and it was probably best.
我把监护权交给他  是为了你能保住你的股份
I gave him custody so you could keep your shares
我是在为你的利益着想
and I could protect your interests.
而且  是你自己选的
You chose.
我要奶油培根和爸爸  谢谢
"I'll have the carbonara and Daddy, please."
我什么都没选
I didn't choose anything.
你一向要什么就有什么
You tend to get what you want anyway.
难道 你不是吗
And you don't?
我觉得我这辈子
I don't think I've ever
就没打过一场胜仗
won a single battle in my whole life.
我那会儿才十岁  妈
I was ten, Mom.
就是个小屁孩而已
I was a fucking kid.
你那会儿十三岁了
You were 13...
你也知道 怎么往伤口上撒盐
and you knew how to twist the knife.
过去现在 一直都是
You knew then and you know now.
我可能会哭
And I might cry.
是吗  洋葱在哪里啊
Oh, yeah, where's the onion?
你那会儿一点都不让我省心
You were quite a piece of work.
你那时是我的洋葱
You were my onion.
你现在也是我的洋葱   -是啊
You are my onion.  Yeah.
你也是我的洋葱
Well, you're my fucking onion.
说实话吧或许我就不该生孩子
Truth is, I probably should never have had children.
你的选择就很对
You made the right decision.
有些人 天生就不是做母亲的料
Some people just aren't made to be mothers.
我就应该养几条狗
I should've had dogs.
你可以养几条狗
-Well, you could've had dogs.
不行  和你爸养的话就算了
-No, not with your father.
他看到心爱之物就想踢一脚
He never saw anything he loved that he didn't wanna kick it
看看他 是否还会回来
just to see if it would still come back.
现在 是什么情况
Okay, what's this?
你爸打了好几通电话
Okay, so your dad called a bunch
但马特森就是不接
and Matsson won't take the calls.
马特森讨庆接电话
Matsson hates the phone.
没什么  我跟爸说过了
That's nothing, I told Dad that.
马特森给我留了通语音
He left me a voice memo,
那推文只是胡闹而已
the tweets were just fucking around.
他的律师在用“公开披露信息法规“吓他
His lawyers have given him the Reg FD scares.
他正飞回瑞士
He's flying back to his Swiss place.
很快就会出面澄清
There's clarification coming.
你爸认为
Yeah. Well, your dad thinks
马特森是想羞辱他
Matsson's trying to humiliate him.
他没有这种想法
Well, he's not.
老爸只需按兵不动
So Dad just needs to ride it out.
我想我们没必要恐慌  格丽
I don't think we need to panic, Gerri. Okay?
我没恐慌   -你有
-I'm not panicking. -I think you are.
因为你搅和了这美妙的夜晚
Because you're interrupting a great night
我正跟劳里打得火热
I'm getting very pally with Laurie.
我可能会尝试干翻他 看他能否
I might try to fuck him see how that
参与我们这段恶心的关系
fits into our disgusting mess.
不要尝试干翻劳里
Do not try to fuck Laurie.
你去和马特森见个面 怎么样
What do you think about going to see Matsson?
当然 可以 老爸希望我去见吗
Yeah. Sure, does Dad want me to?
当然  你爸希望能敲定这桩生意
Yes. Your dad wants the deal.
但你知道的  他们需要一个翻译[中间人]
But, you know, they need a translator.
庄家会面之前  洛根需要得到积极回复
Logan needs reassurance before the banker meet.
好吧  所以  你想要我挽救这笔交易
Okay, so you want me to save the deal?
你怎么不早说  小菜一碟
Why didn't you say so? Piece of cake.
挽救交易  操劳里
Save the deal, fuck Laurie
引领公司走向光明的未来
lead the company into the promised land.
操格丽
fuck Gerri...
这会是很美好的一周的
It's gonna be a great week.
我...我以为只有你和我
I thought this was gonna be private.
我有太多破事要管了
I'm across a lot of shit
她是来监督的
and she's monitoring.
随便逛狂吧  你们..你们可以在里面等
Hang out wherever, you guys can wait inside.
我听说  你问了不少菜单和厨师的问题
So I hear you were asking all about the menu and my chef.
有的东西我吃不了  为了健康着想
Some things are off the menu for me health-wise.
你担心我会给你灌一杯吉姆琼斯吗  再配颗橄榄
You scared I'm gonna try and Jim Jones you with an olive?
这个嘛  我...他们应该带了些吃的来
Well, I think they've brought some food
对我有益的那种
that's good for me.
好吧  那真可惜  马可做菜很好吃
Yeah. It seems a shame, you know, Marco's a great chef.
我们和你的医生核实过了  拿到了膳食要求
So we checked in with your doc and got the requirements.
所以  今天要谈什么
So, what is all this?
你知道的  我...我很忙的
You know, I got a lot to do.
一如既往
As ever.
Gojo 的股价在攀升  而你的好兄弟马特森
GoJo price is spiking and your pal, Matsson
有点不对劲
has got a screw loose.
所以
So
我想我只是想跟你聊聊
I just wanted to talk to you, I suppose.
听我说  我不想现在就开始说  这啊那的
Look, I don't wanna get into it all right now
如果要扯闲话  我马上就会走
because if it's bullshit, I'll just leave.
我们能不能文明点  不要把大家的肠子肚子
Can we be civil and not pull our guts out
摊一桌子
all over the table?
好
-Sure.
那盘... 是他的
That one's for him.
孩子们呢    -他们在屋里
-Where are the kids? -They're inside.
艾弗森
Iverson.
我想打个招呼
I'd like to say hello.
当然
Sure.
小朋友
Hey, kiddo.
最近怎么样
How you doing?
挺好的
Good.
你喜欢马苏里拉奶酪吗
You like mozzarella?
一般般
Not much.
尝尝这个
Try this.
给你尝一口
There you go, try it.
可以  还行
Yeah. It's okay.
你去玩儿吧
Off you go, go on.
凯莉好像给你带了点东西  她在屋里
Kerry has got something for you in there I think.
晚安 小朋友   -晚安
-Good night, buddy. -Night.
你把我想成什么人了
Who do you think I am?
你觉得我想要你的命吗
You think I want you dead?
如果你去世了  我会崩溃的
I'll be broken when you die.
艾弗森最近怎么样
How's the boy doing?
他状态有好点吗
Is he getting better?
他...他还好
He's fine.
所以 听我说.
So look...
我的诉求是..
my thing is,
我想退出
I want out.
我一度以为  我是马背上的骑士
I think I thought I was a knight on horseback
但局势没有照此发展
-but yeah, that isn't panning out.
人生并不是马背上的骑士
-Life's not knights on horseback.
人生就是纸上的一个数字
It's a number on a piece of paper.
是为了泥土里的一把剑 而展开的斗争
It's a fight for a knife in the mud.
我其实不知道...
Like, I don't really know
我的人生将要何去何从
where my life goes from here.
也许我..可以...
Maybe I could...
我不知道
I don't know.
但我不能什么都不做
But I can't do Jack shit.
所以就是
So, here it is,
我想把我的股份溢价变现
I wanna get a premium payout from the holding.
20亿 还有一堆资产
Two bill and a chunky asset.
不用征求股东意见你也能变现的东西
Something you can realize without shareholder input.
可能..
Maybe...
我也不清楚  可能是户外广告播客
I don't know, outdoor advertising, podcasts...
我留下费克雷杰西  然后就走
I keep Fikret, Jess, and I'm gone.
我就是过去式  脱了罗伊家衣服  退出董事会
I'm a ghost, divested, off the board,
完全放弃继承
complete disinheritance.
甚至不会在你的追悼会发言
Won't even speak at your memorial,
我们两清了
we're done.
我需要考虑一下
Well, I need to think about it.
你...你已经
Well, you already...
是你在我生日那天提议的
You offered at my birthday.
那是开玩笑的   -老爸..
That was for fun.  Dad...
我们不能永远这样拉扯
we can't do this bullshit forever.
也许我希望留你在身边呢
Maybe I want you close.
你可以负责邮报  继续在空荡荡的地方工作
You can do the mail, keep you rattling around.
我做不到
I can't.
我试过 但我...我以为 我可以做出一些改变
I tried, but I thought that I could change things...
但我不像..
but I'm not as...
有一些事情  你可以做到  而我不行
There's things you're able to do that I can't,
也许吧
maybe.
也许
Maybe.
你赢了..
You've won...
因为你是腐败的  这个世界也是
because you're corrupt and so is the world.
这个嘛
Well.
我比你好
I'm better than you.
你...我...我不想这么说的
You know, I hate to say this,
因为我爱你 但你有点
because I love you  but you're kind of
恶毒
evil.
自己都不懂的事  就别拿出来说
Don't talk about things you don't understand.
你很聪明
Well, you're smart
但你做过的那些事...你....
but what you've done is you've
利用那些...那些..
monetized all the fucking...
美国人对于阶级和种族的怨恨...来赚钱
The American resentments of class and race and...
我觉得我只是在跟大伙预报天气
And I thought I was just telling folks the weather.
黑胆汁都能被你变成金光闪闪的钱
You've turned black bile into silver dollars.
原来你才发现啊
And you just noticed, did you?
也许我就是才发现吧
Yeah. Maybe I did.
滚蛋吧
Oh, fuck off.
行吧 你知道吗
Fine, you know what?
我他妈根本不在意
I don't give a fuck.
不是每个人都能过这样的人生的
Not everyone can live this life.
我是个伟大的改革者
I'm a great revolutionary.
有一些尖锐
A bit of fucking spice.
一些有趣
-Bit of fun. -Fun.
还有一些真相
A bit of truth.
好吧  真相
Okay. Truth, okay.
我知道这个世界的很多事情
I fucking know things about the world
否则我也不可能赚到钱
or I wouldn't turn a buck.
也许吧   -这些事不一定都是好的
-Maybe. -Not necessarily nice things.
随你怎么说
Look, whatever,
让我退出吧
let me out,
好吗
okay?
付清我的钱  让我退出
Pay up and let me out.
我不想成为你
I don't wanna be you.
我是个好人
I'm a good guy.
那个孩子活了多久..
How long was that kid alive...
在他溺在水里之前
before he started sucking in water?
几分钟吗
Couple of minutes?
三四五分钟吗
Three, four, five?
还是很久呢  亦或是两分钟吗
Long time, two minutes.
那时你又在做什么呢  瞎忙活吗
What were you even doing? Chasing a bit of tail?
难道你是基佬吗
Hey, are you queer?
你当时是想霸王硬上弓吗
Did you try to fuck him?
还是药嗑多了
Or was it just the drugs?
我比你好
-I'm better than you.
当然
-Sure.
你是我儿子嘛
You're my son.
我付出了最大的努力
I did my best...
无论何时你搞砸..
and whenever you fucked up
我都清理了你的屎尿  收拾了你的烂摊子
I cleaned up your shit.
现在 我还是个坏人了
And I'm a bad person?
滚蛋吧  小屁孩儿
fuck off, kiddo.
晚安
Goodnight.
我们要走了
We're out of here.
Gojo在全球范围内的扩张
推文被看作是Gojo进入体育博彩界的迹象
你今晚怎么样
How was your night?
很糟糕  你呢
Awful. You?
还行  罗曼暗示  彼得可能杀了他第一任妻子
Yeah. Roman implied that Peter might have killed his first wife
他还试着焗动劳里
and then he tried to goad Laurie
说一些有关格丽的粗俗话题
into talking indelicately about Gerri.
我们要个孩子吧
Let's have a baby.
真的吗   是的
-Yeah? -Yeah.
汤姆  我他妈的要战斗起来了  好吧
-I'm gonna fucking fight, Tom. -Okay.
汉普顿豪宅[纽约富人区]里的这些东西
Yeah. You don't just get given these things
并不会自己送上门
in a house in the fucking Hamptons.
对  非常对   -不是吗
-Right. Right. -No.
最高职位或者泛美网科 不可能拱手让给你
You know, just get given the top job, or ATN.
我得努力去争取
I'm gonna have to fight for it.
得和格丽 罗曼 还有肯 去争
Gotta fight Gerri and Roman and Ken.
但我能办到  因为我比他们都聪明
But I can because I'm smarter than them.
没错  你是比他们聪明   -没错
-Yes, you are. -Yeah.
我他妈一定能办到
I'm gonna fucking do it.
还有 去咱爸的吧 他想把我踢走多少次都行
And fuck Dad, he can kick me as many times as he wants.
十年或是五年之内
Like ten or five years.
我要开除希德  重建泛美网科
Get rid of Cyd, remake ATN.
是的   -然后毁掉它
-Yeah. -And destroy it
没错   -把它夷为平地 怎么样
-raze it to the ground, yeah? -Yes.
好的  应该是除了我以外吧
Right. I mean, except me.
当然了 除了你   -好
-Yeah. -Yeah, except you.
知道吗  马特森把爸吓到了
You know, and Matsson's got Dad spooked.
所以  我得给爸找个更好的买卖更高的收益
So I'm gonna have to find him a better deal, a bigger one.
我会找到的  我也一定会搞定这笔交易的
I'm gonna do it and I'm gonna fucking nail it, too.
那..那我呢
And what...What about me?
什么... -还有
what... and the...
我们一起啊
Together. Yeah.
因为我们不能让那个龌龊的小鬼登基
Because we can't let the dirty little pixie become king.
不行  是啊  把罗曼挤走
-No. -Yeah. Blow up Roman,
我就是战场上唯一的候选人了
and I'm the only candidate left in the field.
我们尽一切全力吧    你..
Let's do anything, yeah?  -What do you...
好的
-Yeah.
你打算对我做什么   -你太他妈辣了
-What do you wanna do to me? -You're so fucking hot.
你太他妈辣了   -对我说...什么都行
-You're so fucking hot. Just tell me anything,
对我为所欲为
do anything to me.
你..你...
No, you
你先对我说点什么
you say anything to me.
说吧.
Go on,
我的情妇
Mistress
西沃恩·罗伊
Siobhan Roy.
继续
Go on.
你配不上我
You're not good enough for me.
这样啊
Oh, right.
我明白了
Oh. I see.
我们走着瞧  好的
Well, let's see about that. Yeah.
不  你和我远不是一个档次的人
No, I'm way out of your fucking league.
你这么觉得吗  是吗
Oh, you think so? Yeah?
这就是你想要我的原因
But that's why you want me.
这就是为什么.   -或许吧
-That's why  -Maybe.
你爱我
you love me.
操你妹
fuck you.
尽管我不爱你
Even though I don't love you.
但你还是想要我
But you want me anyway.
早上好
Hey.
你偷溜出门了   -是的
-You crept out. -Yeah.
睡得还好吗
Sleep well?
当然  非常好  睡了很久
Oh, yeah. Really good. Lots of sleep.
很抱歉让你又想起这个问题 但很显然
I'm sorry for waking you to ask, but I'm curious,
我很好奇
obviously.
知道  别担心  没事
Yeah. No worries. Yeah.
是的  我 我还在考虑
Yeah, still thinking.
还在考虑   -是的
-Still thinking? -Yeah.
这是个很重大的决定
Big decision,
人生很重大的决定
real life decisions
是的   -所以...
-so just... -Yeah.
行 行  得好好想想
-Right. -Thinking away.
只是考虑这么久  就变得有点不浪漫了
Just, this much thinking could start to get unromantic.
是啊   -我只是说说
-Yeah. -Just saying.
早上好
Hey. -Oh. Wow. -Hey.
这个点了吗
Is that the time?
什么
Excuse me?
只是...只是看一下旧表上的时间
Oh, just checking the old watch there.
我不敢相信
I can't believe it.
你...你今天打算做什么
What are you up to today?
我不知道  工作吧
-I don't know, work shit.
工作
-Work?
是啊   -或者..
Or...
好吧  因为...
Okay, because,
我想 或者说 是我无意听说  你..
I thought, or I've overheard, actually that you...
无意冒犯你
not to intrude, or but...
但...我想 你或许是
But I thought maybe you were part of...
整个
the whole...
君主制的一员
the titled monarchical
这之类的  如果这么说
sort of situation if that's not too bold to say?
不是太过冒味的话
不会  不过  我是做一些
No, sure  but I do a bit of,
我是网络品牌大使
I'm an online brand ambassador.
一种发酵酸奶饮品
A fermented yogurt drink.
发酵酸奶
-Fermented yogurt?
是的   -那...我喝过
-Yeah.  Well, I've had that.
很不错  真的很... 很...
Yeah. It's really good,
是...有清洁肠道的功效
it's a gut cleansing treat.
真的吗   -二货 放开她
-Is it really? -Hey, dipshit. Hands off.
早安   -早安
Hey.
我正赶去拯救世界  应该会在晚饭时回来
I'm just off to save the world. Should be back for dinner.
格雷格
Greg,
你能不能 陪陪这位女伯爵
would you please keep the Contessa company
但别盯着她 谁都知道你在想什么
but don't look at her. Everyone knows what you're thinking
这太恶心了  走了
and it's disgusting, bye-ya!
替他向你道歉
Sorry about him.
劳里  你好吗
-Laurie, how the hell are you?
很好 没错
-I'm good.
很高兴见到你   -对  这就是我表哥
-Good to see you. -Yeah. My cousin.
非常粗鲁的人
A very rude man.
GoJo的价格暴涨了 还高居不下
GoJo price has lurched and held.
都是推特的力量
Power of the tweet.
到周中的时候 他们的市值将要接近我们了
Yeah. By midweek, their market cap is gonna be close to ours.
我觉得 小罗不太可能会成功
I don't think that Rome can find a landing zone for this.
你还好吗
You okay?
昨晚的枕边对话 可真..可真刺激
That was pretty spicy pillow talk last night.
是啊
Yeah.
没错 你好了吗   -好了
-Yeah. You ready? -Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
只不过...那话变得很...
But it did... It got pretty...
你知道的  当你说..
it got pretty... You know, when you said...
说点下流的话
"Say something filthy"
或是"做点低俗的事“时
or "Do something dirty."
怎么了
Mm-hmm?
是啊  我只是很想找乐子  一些少儿不宜的乐子
Yeah. I was just being horrible for fun, you know, dirty fun.
对  那是很下流....但是...
No. It was dirty...
今天早上 我感到有些
but this morning, you know, I feel a little...
有点后劲  你懂吗
A little afterburn, you know.
比方说
Like...
我当时想的...
I was thinking
更多像是情爱珠啊 或是
more like love beads or, you know,
我是性感的消防员啊
I'd be a sexy fireman
但情况却...拐进了
and it was... kind of got into the realms
你不爱我 的领域里
of that you don't love me.
好吧  床上发生的事... [就留在床上吧]
Oh. Okay. Well, what happens in Sex Vegas...
对 对 没错
Right, right, yeah.
我都懂  但有时  我在想..
No, I know, but then sometimes I think...
有时我在想 我是不是应该 把
Sometimes I think should I maybe listen
你在我们最亲热的时候
to the things you say directly in my face
当面对我说的那些话 听进去呢
when we're at our most intimate?
汤姆
Tom,
你不能...我的天
you can't...Oh, my God,
你不能 主动要求别人说坏话 然后
you can't ask someone to say terrible things
又计较
and then get all...
这有点在耍人了
That's a bit manipulative.
是啊  -是吧
-Right. -Yeah.
但你说要孩子  是认真的吗
But did you mean it about the baby?
是的  我
Yes. Yeah, I...
对  我想是的
Yeah, I think so.
迟早会要的
One way or another.
我们至少应该冷冻起来
You know, we should freeze at least.
是吗   -是的
-Yeah? -Yeah.
知道吗  胚胎比卵子存活得更好  所以
You know, embryos survive way better than eggs. So...
我们应该
we should
把它们放在一起  然后看看我们的情况
put it together and then see where we are.
好吧 那你...你觉得 什么时候要 才合适呢
Okay. And when do you think that might be?
我不...
Well,
..我不知道  汤姆  这
I don't know, Tom. I mean,
重要的是...是...
it's important that
子宫要自愿
the host chamber is willing.
他们会保管十年
Well, they keep them for ten years and then
然后 可以随你处置
you can do what you want
但 要是我们其中之一过世 或长期处于昏迷
but it's different if one of us dies
就另当别论了
or is in a long-term coma.
不 这...这是真的
And... No, that's what... It's true.
是真的  你得事先决定好
You decide beforehand
后期 你希望进行的事
what you would want to happen and...
我们如果离婚 或是别的事发生的话
You know, I don't just automatically get them
我不会自动地得到胚胎
if we divorce or something like that,
如果 是这个 让你困扰的话
if that's the thing that concerns you.
不是  我只是说
No, I just...
我就没有想过你刚才说的那事
I wouldn't have necessarily thought about all of that.
好吧  我只是觉得  保存一些胚胎很明智
Well, I just think it's smart to bank some embryos
这样 我们就能走一步看一步了
and then, you know, we can see where we are.
意思是说  我们有可能会等十年吗
So we could be looking at, like, ten years?
那....那就跟...   -这个嘛...
That's like... Oh Well...
十年 差不多够两届半奥运会了
Ten years is like two and a half Olympics.
其实 你要这么说的话
When you put it like that, it's...
不是的
No.
以后情况会更明了的  我只觉得  这是个好的选择
It'll get clearer. I just think it's a good option.
要是出了什么事
And then if something happens
比如 你改了主意 他们就会把胚胎销毁
or, you know, you change your mind they destroy them,
不会有什么栓着你
it doesn't bind you.
要是我死了  我会希望你生我的孩子
I would want you to have my babies if I died.
谢谢你
Thank you.
那要是你死了呢
And if you died?
我会不会想
Would I want...
是啊  应该会吧
Yeah, I think so.
我能想一想吗   -当然了
-Can I think about it? -Sure.
你知道吗  汤姆  我
You know, Tom, I do.
我是有可能不爱你  但我确实爱你啊
I may not love you, but I do love you.
明白吧
You know.
我知道  非常清楚
I know, I do know. I do know.
好
Well...
小孩棒冰
-baby popsicles,
小孩... 小孩棒冰...
baby. -Baby popsicles.
别掉下去了
Don't fall in.
还是算了
Nope
要我拉你一把吗
Do you want me to hold your hand?
喂
Hey.
来啊  我拉你上来
-Come on, I'll hold your hand.
走开
-Piss off.
风景真不错
-Amazing place.
还行吧
-Yeah.
不是吗   -我也说不上来
-No?   -I don't know.
讲道理  这地方还挺唬人的
It kind of freaks me out to be honest.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
刚入手的时候  我想让一切都绝对完美
Well, when I got it, I wanted everything to be absolutely perfect.
结果现在 我就铺一层野营垫子
Now, I'm sleeping on a camping mat
睡地板上  等我找到
on the floor until I get a deep dive
世界上最好的床垫 再换地方
on the best mattress in the world.
所以
So...
其实是很好啦  但是..
-It's great. It's great, but... -Yeah.
我只是 感觉不太对
I'm just not feeling great.
其实 我还...还好
I mean, I'm fine.
好吧  也不是真有多好   -行吧
-Well, but not really. -Okay.
要不 还是把你这点闲愁 收起来吧
Maybe let's leave the little feely-feelings out of it
因为我是不会安慰你的
because I'm gonna give you nothing.
好吧   -不会安慰的
-All right. -Nothing.
所以 从这里望去..
So you got a view here
可以看到湖面   -是啊
-of the lake. -Sure.
有水有船   -对
-Water and boats. -Yeah.
你看啊   -全是水
-Have a gender. -A lot of water.
那个 你最不擅长的是什么
Hey, what are you worst at?
我吗
Me?
对   -最不擅长
-Yeah. -Worst?
成功已经吸引不了我了
Success doesn't really interest me anymore,
太容易了   -是吗
it's too easy.   Uh-huh？
不就是
Like,
分析 加上资本 再加上执行 就这
analysis, plus capital, plus execution.
这玩意....
It's fucking...
谁都会
Anyone can do that.
但是失败..
But failure...
就很神秘了
You know, that's a secret.
我要失败  越多越好
Just as much failure as possible,
越快越好
as fast as possible.
要一败涂地
Just burn that shit out.
我嘛...   -那才好玩
-Well, I... -That's interesting.
才不会告诉你
...am not telling you
我的任何一个弱点呢  永远不会
a single one of my weaknesses, ever.
想都别想
Ever...
绝不   -你还挺聪明的
-Ever... -That's smart.
我知道  我就是聪明
I know. I'm smart.
要知道  我最会骗人了
Because I ream people.
我会把人像橘子一样榨干
Juice them like oranges.
好了  说正经的  我
No, look, seriously...
我实在太喜欢人了
I get way too into people and...
但是他们老让我失望
And then they disappoint me.
对了  我
Hey, I'm
在考虑  在公司里
thinking of doing, like a quarterly up
来一个季度性裁员不升即走
or outs at the company.
不错啊   -对
-Oh, yeah. -Yeah.
我每天早上起床的动力  85%来源于炒别人鱿鱼
Firing people is like 85% of why I get up in the morning.
但是
But...
我还想问问你  那条推特是怎么回事
do wanna ask you about that tweet,
你不介意的话
if you don't mind.
那个..
Oh  the
那个啊   -对说正经的
-That one? -Yeah. Seriously. Yes.
有 天上掉下的大馅饼 砸到你了吗
You got, like, big shit coming your way?
兄弟  你是不是
Dude, are you...
你是在问我要 非公开信息吗
Are you asking me for material non-public information?
我也不知道
I mean, I don't know.
你是不是想通过 在正常信息公开渠道之外的地方
Were you trying to give your share price a pop
发布一些无法核实的信息
by tweeting unverifiable information
来抬高自己的股价呢
outside normal disclosure channels?
不行  你不许那么做
No. You're not allowed to do that.
是啊  -太卑鄙了
-Yup. -So mean.
我需要知道的是...
The thing I need to know is
你到底想不想跟我们交易  你认真考虑了这件事吗
do you want this deal? Are you into it at all?
想啊  当然了   -好
-Yeah, I am. -Okay.
我只是有点瑞典人的个性  你知道吧
I'm just a little Swedish, you know?
坚持平等原则,   -好吧
-I'm into equality. -Okay.
我喜欢跟人上床[结盟]
I like getting into bed with people,
但我也喜欢跟人平等分享
but I also like sharing it equally.
好的
Okay.
好吧  是这样  我要去米兰
Okay. It's just... I'm heading to Milan
跟老爸和庄家把事情定下来
to lock things down with Dad and the bankers,
但是
and...
那条推特让人感觉不对劲
the tweet just didn't feel great.
要是你想 放弃我们商量好的事情
And if you're hoping to just blow this whole thing up
直说就行了  好吗
just tell me, okay?
我不过是想要最好的东西罢了
I just wanna get myself the best of everything.
好啊
Okay.
妈的  我懂你  这必须的啊
fuck yeah. I get that. Definitely.
来啦   -来啦
-Hey. -Hey.
怎么说
So?
我感觉没戏了   -什么
-So I think it's over. -What?
对  我感觉马特森不想被收购
Yeah, I don't think Matsson's interested in getting acquired.
他是要争取跟我们对等合并
I think he's angling for a merger of equals.
行吧  妈的
Okay. fuck.
所以 已经没救了 对吧   -好吧
-Well? -So it's dead, right?
你确定吗   -这个嘛...
-Are you sure? -Well...
我不想增加你的压力  罗曼
I mean, I don't wanna pile on the pressure, Roman
当然了  我们还是有很多条路可以走下去的
and, obviously, there are always multiple ways forward
我不想过度关注这一个选项  但是
and I don't wanna overcook this but
要说有意义的交易的话
in terms of deals that make sense
如果我们不尽快壮大实力  很快就要成为别人的盘中餐了
if we don't beef up soon, I think we end up someone's lunch.
好  谢谢你  小格
Well, thanks, Ger.
我已经紧张得撸空气了
I'm already so stressed I'm jerking dust.
跟我一起去告诉他吗
You want to tell him together?
我这里头的事情参与不多  所以...
I'm not really inside the details, so...
好吧  那是自然
Okay. Sure.
很高兴先跟你打了招呼  回头见
-Well, it was nice knowing you then..
行
-Yep
在我们 把杂牌马戏团[庄家] 请到现场之前
So before we get the whole three-ring circus in here
先朋友之间说说
just among friends
我想知道  到底是怎么一回事
I wanna get a sense of what's going on.
他是那种在推特上口无遮拦的人
Is he a Twitter panty flasher?
还是个正经严肃的人
Or is he a serious person?
他是个正经严肃的人
Well, he is a serious person.
你确定吗
You're certain?
是的  小西  他很严肃
Yes, Shiv, he is serious.
但是  爸他
But, Dad,
他觉得 现在谈的价钱 还达不到他公司的价值
he thinks there's value that hasn't been priced in yet.
马特森正在竭力促成对等合并
Matsson's gunning for a merger of equals.
所以 我猜 你懂的 或许
So I guess, you know, that probably...
对等合并
-Merger of equals?
对  他成功地让12个主要的亚洲体育联赛
-Yeah.  Like he's got 12 of the prime Asian sports leagues
签了GoJo  他要把这些内容 一股脑塞到平台里
signed up for GoJo and he's gonna fold it all in to the platform.
体育直播比赛 体彩 这他妈是要实现爆炸式增长
Live sports, games, betting. It's a fucking growth bomb.
好吧  但...董事会席位会对半开  放弃以前的股份
Okay. But, full 50-50 board, all stock.
怎么  他还想和爸分权吗
-Dad, what, splits control?
是的  西沃恩
-Yes, Siobhan.
我不..   -我知道
Well, I don't...
我觉得不..爸
I don't think... Dad?
但那家伙 不是个傻子吧
But the guy isn't a fuckhead?
不 那条推特是他的计谋
No. The tweeting was a move.
他不是什么博取点击率的巨婴吧
Well, he's not some big baby who shits for clicks?
不 不是...他很有心计
No. No. He's on the snake.
我很会看人的  爸  我对人的嗅觉很敏锐
You know, I know people, Dad. I'm a people sniffer.
任何拳击赛  我穿条短裤就能拿下
Because I can win any bout with a boxer fuck
但我不知道怎么击倒一个小丑
but I don't know how to knock out a clown.
他不是小丑  他是个狠人
He's not a clown. He's a motherfucker.
换你也会这样做  不是吗
It's what you would have done, right?
他只是把杠杆比率最大化了
He just maximized his leverage.
那  对等合并算什么
Yeah, but "merger of equals?" Like...
没有的事  -总是想当领头狗  对吧
-No such thing. -Always a top dog, right?
对  他是想要名号
Sure. And I mean he wants the label
但我觉得  我们还是可以压他一头的吧
but I think we could still be the puppy fuckers here?
家族股份会被
The family stake will be
严重稀释
seriously diluted.
他应该会让我们负责这方面
I think he'd let us craft it so that
这样我们才能维持董事会的平衡
we keep balance of the board.
他应该只是想要自由和地位
I think he just wants the freedom and the status.
Gojo 罗伊科公司  谁他妈在乎啊
GoJo Royco. I mean, who gives a fuck?
他想要标志就拿去  我们掌权
Let him have the logo, we take the wheel.
我同意  这会是真正的大规模
Yeah, I mean, it would be real scale.
并且 这样的联系是合法的
It's a legitimate way of staying relevant.
这是场巨大的剧变
It's a big upheaval.
当然  高层的话...
Yeah, I mean the top team will...
你们本来也是为生计拼搏
You know, you'll be obviously be fighting for your lives.
但你们可以相信爸  朋友们
But I'm sure you can trust Dad, guys.
当然了
Obviously.
合并能行得通  对吧
Merger's really a state of mind, right?
爸  格丽  还是你们掌舱
Dad, Gerri, you stay with your hands on the tiller.
毕竟他们的价格涨幅...真实可见
I mean, their price rise, it's real.
这他妈的是一家有前途的流媒体
It's a proper fucking streamer.
未来就是
And the future is
电影 电视 音乐 游戏 体育 电子体育
movies, TV, music, games, sports, eSports
虚拟现实 增强现实 赌博 什么都有
VR, AR, betting, fucking everything,
人人都适用  马特森知道该怎么做到
for everyone  and Matsson knows how to get there.
洛根
Logan?
我们现在不能一走了之  代价太大
We can't afford to walk away right now.
一定是值得谈一场的 儿子
Must be worth a conversation, son.
带他们进来
Bring them in.
让庄家都进来搅搅局
Let's get the banker fucks in here on this.
好的
Okay.
成了
fucking A.
【格丽·吉尔曼】
干的好 罗曼
这边走
Right this way.
这位是汤姆·威姆士丹  泛美网科新闻部的主席
This is Tom Wambsgans...he's the Chairman of ATN News.
你好  -你好
-Hi. -Hi.
我是汤姆  你好吗    -挺好
-Hello. How are you? -Good.
这位是小西·罗伊  国内运营部总裁
Shiv Roy, President of Domestic Operations.
【新建短信】
共进庆功晚餐吗 格丽? 吃这个吧
很高兴见到你   -格丽·吉尔曼
【爸】
干的很好 儿子
共进庆功晚餐吗 格丽? 吃这个吧
请大家随便坐
Sit wherever you're comfortable.
等我五分钟
I need five.
爸
Dad?
天哪  我操
Jesus. fuck.
对  是他的屌  他
Yeah, that's his dick.
不小心把屌照发给你了
He's sent you a picture of his dick by mistake.
显然是这样
Well, it's pretty obvious.
他本来要发给格丽的
Yeah, he meant to send it to Gerri.
我没明白
I don't get it.
他..其实吧
Well, honestly,
他对格丽怪怪的
he's weird about Gerri.
大家都知道
Everyone knows it. And...
说实话  我觉得这很恶心
And, frankly, I think it's fucking disgusting.
是吗
-Yeah?
是的  格丽大概...
-Yeah. Yeah, Gerri is probably
出于利益 没有阻止他
just not stopping it for leverage.
留这些作为把柄
You know, banking it as ammo.
他难道不是在小打小闹吗
Isn't he just Roman being Roman?
不
No.
我觉得不是..更像是
No, I mean... No, I think it's
潜在隐患
a potential problem.
这有问题  你知道吗
There's issues, you know?
大家都说 他以前被私人教师
Everyone says they used to get jerked off by his personal trainer.
现在 又和格丽这样
And now there's this Gerri thing.
这是...
It's a...
这是有迹可循的
It's a track record, you know?
所以 我认为往后的日子里
So I think, you know, moving forward
也许应该...  -好了 可以了
perhaps we should... Oh, okay...
谢谢你  谢了 小宝
Well, thank you. Thank you, Pinkie.
回去吧   -好的
Go on. -Okay.
罗曼!   我靠
-Roman! -Jesus, fuck.
帮你说了几句好话
Hey, put in a good word for you.
谢谢
Thanks.
你有病吗
Are you a sicko?
这是什么   -老天
-What is this? -Oh, Jesus.
你为什么要发   -靠 就是
Why do you send them?   God, it's just, you know,
就是
it's like...
请看我的屌
"Here's my dick."
所以呢  你的意思就像..“去你的"吗
Oh, what? Like a fuck you?
人们就是会互相发屌照啊
People just send each other pics of their dicks.
人们就是会互相发屌照
People send each other pics of their dicks?
对啊   你听说过屌照吗  爸
Yeah. Have you heard of dick pics, Dad?
我们的确发行了很多畅销报纸
Well, we do publish a number of popular newspapers
所以  儿子  我听过
so yes, son
这个词没准还是我们造的
we probably invented the fucking words.
但 为什么
But why?
为什么   我不知道
Why? I don't know.
就是“请看我的屌”我猜是这样吧
It's just like, here's my dick, I guess.
你是有什么问题吗
You got a problem?
和你在一起的那个漂亮小妞 怎么样了
What happened to that nice piece of tail you were with?
塔比莎吗  她很不错
Tabitha? Yeah, she's amazing.
我们有些争吵
We're having some issues
然后
and...
格丽到底哪里吸引你
What interests you in Gerri exactly?
我靠  爸..我就是在到处乱搞
Jesus, Dad. I'm fucking... I'm screwing around!
我不喜欢有人背着我搞事
I don't like things going on I don't know about.
她都一大把年纪了
She's a million years old.
太他妈反胃了
It's fucking disgusting.
你就是笑柄
You're a laughingstock.
回去吧  滚吧
Oh, go on, fuck off.
现在是什么情况
So like what happens now?
我不想再看到 她在我眼前晃来晃去
I don't want her hanging around like frozen fucking piss.
格丽吗
Gerri?
我虽然不是激进的女权主义者  爸
I'm not a radical feminist, Dad
但我觉得  也许不该因为
but I think perhaps we should not fire her
她收到了我的屌照 就开除她吧
for receiving pictures of my dick.
你要回会议室吗
Are you gonna come back?
不好意思把你请出来  格丽
Sorry about all this, Gerri.
我就是想搞清楚...
It's just something I wanna get...
到底发生了什么  好吗
you know, really clear about what's going on, you know?
最重要的是  确认你有没有事
And most importantly, to see if you're okay.
这...不是什么大事
-It's not a big deal.
好的  我只是想把事情搞清楚
-Okay.  Yeah, I just wanna get things clear
为了我爸  懂吧
for my dad, you know?
天啊  一定很难吧
God, this must be so hard for you.
没事的   -你想不想
-It's fine. -Do you wanna...
不坐吗   好的
No? Okay.
所以  这个事或类似这样的事  以前发生过吗
So has this or something like this happened before?
我记不起来了
I can't recall.
假设发生过  你有让他别做了吗
And if it did, did you ask him to stop?
我们明天再聊  可以吗
Let's talk about this tomorrow, okay?
还有其他人在等我
I just need to check-in with some people.
好的  当然可以  你并没有
Okay. Well, sure. I mean, it's not...
你并不乐意收到这些
It's not as if you were welcoming
东西
these items...
我说得对吗  格丽
-were you, Gerri?
小西
-Shiv.
听着  我们必须要搞清楚
Look, it's just something for your wellbeing
这 事关你的身心健康  因为..
we need to get really clear about because,
你知道的
you know,
我们有可能即将迎来剧变
with all this potential upheaval
你又是临时首席执行官  这个位置很微妙
and you being in such a delicate position as interim CEO
如果你不能解决自己的性骚扰问题
if you can't deal with your own sexual harassment
那可就不好看了
then it's not a good look.
我能处理
I can cope.
好的  你想对他的行为
Okay. So do you wanna make a formal complaint
提交正式投诉吗
against him regarding this?
这由我自己决定
-Well, that's for me to decide.
我只是在想  格丽...
I just think, Gerri,
你该向人事部门举报他  因为如果你不这样
that you should report him to HR because if you don't,
可能会招来争议  比如说  你乐意接收这些照片.
it could be argued  that you welcomed these photos
这可有损你的地位
and that just undermines your position.
这  只是...只是我的担心
It's just... That's my concern for you here.
我在想  是不是该
I wonder if we shouldn't
直接向董事会公开这些
just kick this all the way up to the board?
谢谢你为我考虑了这么多
Well, thank you for giving this so much thought.
我会好好想想的  好吗  -好
-And I'll think it over, okay? -Okay.
会议室见  想好了告诉我
-So I'll see you back inside. -Let me know.
老爸  我要和苏菲一起进屋了
Hey, Dad, I think I'm gonna head inside with Soph.
好的  小子
Okay, buddy.